Department of Biological Sciences fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Departmental files, 1964 - 1985; F-5-5; 1.64 m of textual records
  - C.D. Nelson Memorial Fund, 1968 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 5-11)
  - Patents and copyrights, 1965 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 5-11)
  - Equipment, 1968 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 5-11)
  - Research equipment, 1968 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 5-11)
  - Support staff job descriptions and classifications, 1966 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Modified work week, 1972 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Teaching assistants - general, 1967 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Teaching assistants - policy, 1975 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Teaching assistants - traineeships, 1974 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Ministry of Labour - research support, 1975 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
  - Research - general, 1971 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 5-12)
    Open
  - Research - biohazards, 1977 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - marine biology, 1968 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - microbiology, 1968; F-5-5-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - pest management, 1967 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - photobiology, 1968 - 1970; F-5-5-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - plant biology, 1973 - 1974; F-5-5-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - pollution, 1968 - 1975; F-5-5-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Research - current interests, 1976; F-5-5-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - animal care, 1968 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - TV ecology, F-5-5-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - continuing education, 1970 - 1974; F-5-5-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - continuing education, 1972 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - continuing education, 1976 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - long range planning, 1966 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 5-13)
  - Teaching - loads, 1967 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Teaching - methods, 1967 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Teaching - tri-semester system, 1967 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - High school relations, 1967 - 1975; F-5-5-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - general, 1971 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - admissions, 1967 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - general, 1973 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - brochures, 1967 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - course offerings, 1967 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 5-14)
  - Graduate students - curriculum, 1967 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - enrollments, 1969 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - M.Sc. Education, 1974; F-5-5-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - graduate record exam, 1967 - 1972; F-5-5-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - MPM program, 1974 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - procedures, 1969 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Graduate students - supervisory committees, 1967 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Teaching - undergraduates - marine science, 1972 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Teaching - undergraduates - queries, 1967 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Teaching - undergraduates - questionnaires, 1972 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Associations and memberships - Burnaby Aquarium of Ecology, 1967; F-5-5-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Associations and memberships - TRIUMF, 1968 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Government agencies - Atomic Energy of Canada Limited, 1967 - 1969; F-5-5-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Government agencies - Canadian Department of the Environment, 1967 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Government agencies - National Museum, 1972 - 1973; F-5-5-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Government agencies - Canadian Science Secretariat, 1967 - 1971; F-5-5-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 5-15)
  - Marine biology - Bamfield, 1975 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Interdisciplinary studies - biochemistry, 1967 - 1974; F-5-5-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Interdisciplinary studies - environmental studies, 1971 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - general, 1971 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - course changes, 1966 - 1975; F-5-5-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - course offerings, 1966 - 1979; F-5-5-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - transfer credits - general, 1967 - 1977; F-5-5-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - transfer credits - BCIT, 1974 - 1976; F-5-5-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 5-16)
  - Undergraduates - curriculum, 1967 - 1971; F-5-5-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Undergraduates - curriculum, 1972 - 1975; F-5-5-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Undergraduates - curriculum, 1971 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Undergraduates - enrollments, 1966 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Library, 1978 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Public relations (Open House), 1979 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 5-17)
  - Bursaries, fellowships, scholarships - general, 1978 - 1982; F-5-5-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 5-18)
  - Word processing systems, 1979 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 5-18)
  - Word processing systems, 1980 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 5-18)
  - Continuing studies, 1978 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 5-18)
  - Articulation and transfer credits, 1978 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 5-18)
  - High school mentor program, 1980 - 1984; F-5-5-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings and outlines, 1978 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings, 1980 - 1982; F-5-5-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings, 1979 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings, 1977 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings - special topic courses, 1977 - 1982; F-5-5-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - Course offerings - Bamfield Marine Station, 1978 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 5-19)
  - History of course enrolments, 1968; F-5-5-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - History of course enrolments, 1972 - 1973; F-5-5-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - History of course enrolments, 1974 - 1975; F-5-5-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - History of course enrolments, 1976; F-5-5-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - History of course enrolments, 1977 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - History of course enrolments, 1979; F-5-5-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - History of course enrolments, 1983; F-5-5-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - Patterns of Development in the Faculty of Science, 1969; F-5-5-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - status of program, 1978 - 1979; F-5-5-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - visitors, 1978; F-5-5-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - interuniversity correspondence, 1978 - 1979; F-5-5-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - courses - BISC 847, 1977 - 1978; F-5-5-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - Director's correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-5-5-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - MPM - Director's correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-5-5-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 5-25)
  - Public relations, 1981 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Arts, Education and Interdisciplinary Studies, 1978 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Biological Sciences Merit Award, 1978 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Continuing studies, 1980 - 1983; F-5-5-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Long range planning, 1977 - 1982; F-5-5-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Co-op education in Biological Sciences, 1980 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 5-26)
  - Course offering - general, 1982 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 5-27)
  - Course offerings - special topic courses, 1980 - 1985; F-5-5-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 5-27)
- Curriculum and programs, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6; 57 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the courses offered by the department, including course content, requirements, expectations and examinations. It includes correspondence, course outlines, sample examination papers, and reports.
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 003, 1969 - 1975; F-5-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 5-20)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 101, 1969 - 1972; F-5-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 5-20)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 101, 1973 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 5-20)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 102, 1968 - 1971; F-5-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 5-20)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 102, 1972 - 1974; F-5-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 5-20)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 102, 1975 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 105 and 201, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 202, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 203, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 204, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 300, 1969 - 1975; F-5-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 5-21)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 301, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 302, 1969 - 1977; F-5-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 303 and 304, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 305, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 306, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 310 and 315, 1968 - 1977; F-5-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 316, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 5-22)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 317, 1969 - 1977; F-5-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 326, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 336 and 337, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 346 and 347, 1970 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 400 and 401, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 404 and 405, 1968 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 5-23)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 407-410, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 417, 418 and 424, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 428, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 430, 432, 435, 438, 447, 448, 455 and 481, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 601-605, 1974; F-5-6-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
  - Course outlines and examinations - BISC 808, 810, 816, 821, 834, 840-842, 844, 845, 847, 848, 859, 1969 - 1978; F-5-6-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 5-24)
- Centre for Pest Management files, 1962 - 1979; F-5-7; 1 m of textual records
  The chief function of the Centre for Pest Management was the administration and promotion of pest management research and the provision of instruction. In meeting this responsibility, its Director worked to forge links with other universities, research institutes and professional associations, as well as to attract eminent pest management experts, entomologists and plant pathologists to give guest lectures or conduct research. It also provided a place of instruction for students in all degree programs.
  Series consists of records relating to the administrative and operational activities and responsibilities of the Centre. It includes meeting agenda and minutes, correspondence, course and program proposals and outlines, directives, proposals, published materials, reports, and working papers.
  - Director's correspondence and reports, 1962 - 1973; F-5-7-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - The Belleville-Simon Fraser Affair, 1962 - 1967; F-5-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Pestology Centre, 1969 - 1973; F-5-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
  - Printed materials, 1968 - 1974; F-5-7-2; 1 cm of textual records
    - Pestology Centre brochures and pamphlets, 1968 - 1974; F-5-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
  - Curricula and programs, 1971 - 1976; F-5-7-3; 8 cm of textual records
    - Proposed course and program changes, 1971; F-5-7-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Proposal for a new Master's degree and program in Pest Management, 1972; F-5-7-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Course outlines (600 level), 1974; F-5-7-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Course outlines (600 level), 1975; F-5-7-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Course outlines (600 level), 1976; F-5-7-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
    - Course outlines (600 level), 1976; F-5-7-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 5-35)
  - Office files, 1964 - 1979; F-5-7-4; 87 cm of textual records
    International Advisory Committee for Biological Control; Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization; Science Council of Canada; International Development Research Centre; Canada. Agriculture Canada; Canadian International Development Agency; International Crops Research Institute for Semi-Arid Tropics; Environment Canada; British Columbia. Department of Agriculture; United States. Department of Agriculture; National Research Council; Defence Research Board; Oregon State University; University of British Columbia (UBC); Memorial University of Newfoundland; University of California; Department of Biological Sciences; University Library; Commonwealth Institute of Biological Control; University of the West Indies
    - Filing index for Pestology Centre (1967-1971 inclusive), F-5-7-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence, 1966; F-5-7-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence, 1967; F-5-7-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-5-7-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence and reports, 1964; F-5-7-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence and reports, 1966; F-5-7-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 5-36)
    - International Biological Program correspondence and reports, 1967 - 1970; F-5-7-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Biological Program - Pacific Science Congress, 1970 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Advisory Committee for Biological Control correspondence, 1966; F-5-7-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Advisory Committee for Biological Control correspondence, 1967; F-5-7-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Advisory Committee for Biological Control correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-5-7-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Advisory Committee for Biological Control correspondence, 1965 - 1967; F-5-7-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - Symposium on Systematic Entomology, 1969; F-5-7-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - International Organization for Biological Control, 1968 - 1970; F-5-7-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization, 1968 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - Science Council of Canada - correspondence, 1968 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 5-37)
    - National Research Council - correspondence, 1967 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - National Research Council - Negotiated Development Grant, 1967 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - National Research Council - grants, 1967 - 1969; F-5-7-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Visitors, 1967 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Pestology faculty correspondence, 1967 - 1971; F-5-7-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Proposed programs (DPM and MPM), 1971; F-5-7-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Bird hazard research, 1971; F-5-7-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Biology staff meetings, 1967 - 1968; F-5-7-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 5-38)
    - Biology staff meetings, 1967 - 1968; F-5-7-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Crown Zellerbach, 1976 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - International Biological Program correspondence, 1972 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Commonwealth Institute of Biological Control, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Science Council of Canada, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - International Development Research Centre - Tsetse Control Meeting, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Government of Canada, 1972 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Agriculture Canada - Ontario, 1974 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Agriculture Canada - British Columbia, 1972 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Agriculture Canada - Ontario, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Canadian International Development Agency, 1971 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - International Development Research Centre, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - International Crops Research Institute for Semi-Arid Tropics, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Environment Canada - general, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - Environment Canada - Ontario, 1972 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - B.C. Department of Agriculture - general, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - B.C. Department of Agriculture - Royal Commission of Inquiry into the Use of Pesticides and Herbicides, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 5-39)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture - general, 1972 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - National Research Council - correspondence, 1972 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Defence Research Board - general, 1974; F-5-7-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Universities - general, 1972 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Oregon State University - general, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - University of British Columbia, 1971 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Memorial University of Newfoundland, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - University of California, 1973; F-5-7-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Pestology - general correspondence, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Liaison with other institutes and agencies, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Pestology - visitors, 1972 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Pestology - requests for technical information, 1971 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Bud worm spray correspondence, 1977; F-5-7-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Correspondence with Pestology faculty, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Proposed programs - DPM and MPM, 1972; F-5-7-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Proposed programs - DPM and MPM, 1973 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Buildings, 1973; F-5-7-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 5-40)
    - Survey of programs at SFU re: MPM, 1973; F-5-7-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Drafts of brochures for MPM programs, 1973 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-61 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM - general, 1973 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM - capital planning, 1973; F-5-7-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM - progress of program, 1973 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM - admissions policy, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM - courses, 1973 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Cost of MPM program, 1974 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - MPM examinations, 1974 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-68 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Pest Management Association Newsletter, 1975 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Inter-university correspondence, 1972 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Biological Sciences correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 5-41)
    - Biological Sciences correspondence, 1975 - 1977; F-5-7-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - President's Office, 1973 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-73 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Vice-presidents' Offices, 1972 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Library, 1972 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-75 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Pestology Director's correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-5-7-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Pestology Director's correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-5-7-4-0-77 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Pestology Director's correspondence, 1977; F-5-7-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Pestology Director's correspondence - Dr. Jaroslav Weiser, 1970 - 1973; F-5-7-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Environmental programs, 1974 - 1975; F-5-7-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - University of the West Indies, 1977 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Liaison with other agencies, 1977 - 1978; F-5-7-4-0-82 (Archival box - standard 5-42)
    - Commonwealth Institute of Biological Control, 1978 - 1979; F-5-7-4-0-83 (Archival box - standard 5-42)